ADAPTED FROM THE LEGEND
OF KUNSHAN JADE BY TAN TIANYIN
It's beautiful.
-Everyone will be impressed.
-Yeah.
Xue.
CLEAR MIND
Today is the opening day of Clear Mind.
Lady Bai,
are you here to congratulate Ms. Su?
I forgot.
Did you get kicked
out of Zhenlang Pavilion?
Xue.
Did you pay your respects to Lady Yu?
We don't have to do that.
We are all shareholders of Clear Mind.
With your money,
Clear Mind shouldn't be running for long.
Nonsense.
I'm telling you.
One of our shareholders
is a Zheng.
Forget it.
Let's go.
Clear Mind's stuff is beautiful.
Yeah. Let's come here again tomorrow.
This hairpin is delicate.
Master.
How can people be so shameless?
Bai Niao came here
and wanted to see you.
I mocked her.
Today is the opening day of Clear Mind
across the street.
The street is crowded.
The shop is busy.
It makes our shop very deserted.
How do we do business?
How can they do business like that?
Master, don't worry.
I'll smash their shop.
What's wrong with you?
Their business has nothing to do with us.
If you are free, count our inventory
and settle the accounts.
This table is dirty. Clean it.
You never cared about that.
Master.
Do you feel like
you're facing a great enemy?
Facing a great enemy?
Nonsense.
People who buy ten-cashes jewelry
are not our target customers.
Of course.
The shop that sells ten-cashes jewelry
is not our opponent.
What are you talking about?
Master, good for you.
By the way,
Zhang Jinran
will come to Yangzhou soon.
He was appointed
as Inspector of Huainandao.
When he arrives, he will be good for us
and for Clear Mind.
Should we give him some clues?
He should know what to do.
He used to be a scholar.
Now, he's a high-ranking official
with real power.
After all, he's still Zhang Jinran.
ZHENLANG PAVILION
CLEAR MIND
Do you have wine?
No. I only have tea.
Tea is good for you.
It can make you sober.
It's mine.
It's not yours.
I took a fancy to it first.
Did you pay for it?
I can pay right away.
Your opening day looks lively.
But it's not good for your business.
Most of your customers
are the common people.
If Clear Mind gives people
the impression of being cheap,
the rich and noble families
will give it up.
You should know
that jewelry is not just about beauty.
It's a symbol of status.
You're right.
Zhenlang Pavilion, Jubao House,
Baicaojing House, and Zhenbao House
are symbols of status.
If I want
to stand out among these jewelry shops,
I have to rely on these common ladies.
Clear Mind can please them.
They can also please me.
You have a point.
You have an idea.
We came to Yangzhou together.
But in such a short time,
you opened a big shop
opposite Zhenlang Pavilion.
And you're fighting with Yan Zijing.
Forget about my advice.
I underestimated you.
Thankfully,
we are both targeting Yan Zijing.
Yes.
If it weren't for Yan Zijing,
I wouldn't have opened Clear Mind.
But we are different.
Clear Mind is my business,
not my sword.
Have you forgotten your blood feud?
Have you forgotten Shrimp
and the dead of the trading convoy?
They are waiting for you to avenge them.
That's why
I said
we are different.
Huan.
I brought you jewelry.
It's yours.
You won the top beauty title.
You can't retire.
It's a waste of your good years.
I know you're mad at me.
You know how the Huan family is.
You won the top beauty title.
We'll make a difference.
In the future,
the Huan family will support you
at any cost.
It wasn't easy raising you
all these years.
When you were a baby,
I picked you up from the snow.
-You can't be--
-Ungrateful?
Did the Huan family do anything
to support me in winning
the top beauty title?
As for you raising me,
I've paid you back with all the money
I've made you over the years.
The jewelry
was mine.
Mr. Huan, please leave.
From now on, I have nothing to do
with the Huan family.
Huan, do you want to leave
the Huan family?
Please leave.
Do you think
Clear Mind can be your support?
Dream on.
It won't take long for you
to come back crying and begging me.
Zhenlang Pavilion's jewelry
is gorgeous.
Mr. Yan, you're from the Western Regions.
You must know where to buy it.
I do.
If the Western Regions colored stones
sell well in Yangzhou,
would you like to sell them?
Of course.
Mr. Yan, we're counting on you.
Mr. Yan, you're generous.
Jades are fine and simple.
Pearls are elegant and noble.
Golds are brilliant and magnificent.
Western Regions colored stones
are colorful.
But they are kitsch.
They are no match
for Central Plains jewelry.
Mr. Zheng, you're right.
Have you heard
that Su Muzhe
opened a shop?
It's called Clear Mind, right?
It's inappropriate for a woman
to open a shop.
It's a disgrace to the jewelry industry.
Anyway, she opened the shop.
And she's doing great.
Her customers lined up
all the way to my stop this morning.
Maybe she has a skill.
Mr. Zheng.
A woman opened a shop in Yangzhou.
But she didn't inform us.
I don't think it's appropriate.
In my opinion,
we should cut off her gold and raw stones.
Let's see what she can do.
Yeah.
-You have a point.
-Yeah.
Clear Mind's shareholders are Zheng Wu
and some songstresses.
They can't resist the suppression
of the jewelry guild.
When she opened her shop here,
she should have thought about that.
Are you going to help her?
I won't help her this time.
She doesn't want me to help.
If she wants to get a foothold here,
she has to go through this.
So she can grow.
Let's get to business.
The Black Dragon Bandits
have been dormant since the last time.
They robbed once last month.
We haven't found
their base yet.
They will sell
what they robbed.
Only the Zheng family
can help them sell their robbed goods.
What are we going to do?
I heard that Prince Ying
ordered a birthday gift
for the Empress Dowager at Jubao House.
Have you found the escorts?
Yes, Master.
I found the best escorts.
You must be cautious.
Send the Red Leaf Crown
to Chang'an safely.
Yes.
Master, Hexi got some goods.
They informed us to pick it up.
Prince Ying told us not to trade recently.
Why did they ignore it?
What should we do?
The cargo ship
is about to arrive in Yangzhou.
If we don't pick it up,
it would be more dangerous.
Those goods
are dangerous.
Why didn't you just play the pipa?
Why did you follow Clear Mind
and change your plan?
You lost the top beauty title.
Do you know how much it affects
Baicaojing House's business?
Mr. Qin, ease up.
Shut up.
Are you upset?
Okay, I won't blame you.
If you go to your patron,
won't he blame you?
What's wrong?
He didn't see you?
You ended up losing everything.
We can't rely on the Zheng family.
The patron doesn't want to see you.
Even Zhenlang Pavilion
doesn't invest in you.
What should we do?
Don't forget
that I opened Baicaojing House for you.
Watch your attitude.
You're like my own sister.
You should support me.
GRACIOUS COURTYARD OF ORCHIDS AND JADE
Let me see.
Does it still hurt?
Be careful.
Ask Xuanji to help you with your work.
Tomorrow, I'll get you a good doctor
to change the dressing.
You'll be able to play the pipa again
in a few days.
As long as you can play the pipa,
Baicaojing House's business
will get better and better.
Don't be upset.
I didn't mean it.
I'm doing it for your own good.
You're like my own sister.
I love you.
As long as you're good,
Baicaojing House will be good.
Speaking of business,
Niao, I need more money.
Why are you asking me for money again?
I just gave you money.
Mu, spend more time on business.
If you have time,
go to Clear Mind
and look at their designs.
Hire some skilled craftsmen.
Baicaojing House's jewelry
is out of date.
You have a point, Niao.
That's why I need new designs
and new goods.
Do you think I'm asking you for money
for yourself?
It's for business.
Give me some money. I can make more money.
Go.
Don't worry, Niao.
I have a plan.
About the new goods…
What are you thinking about?
I'm telling you.
One of our shareholders
is a Zheng.
Who are you trying to set up?
Think of a way to tell the Zheng family
that Zheng Wu invested in Clear Mind
behind their back.
He supported Lady Huan
at the Qionghua Festival.
I knew Zheng Wu had money.
If you hooked him, the top beauty title…
I'll shut up. Don't be mad.
I'll do what you say.
Master.
Turn around.
Hero. Please spare my life.
-Don't move.
-Please spare my life. You…
I'll give you as much as you want.
Don't take that.
I'll be beheaded.
Please don't.
No.
Um…
Are you saying
that they didn't want to take it away?
Yes.
They smashed the Red Lead Crown
and left.
They wanted to ruin my big thing.
It's a birthday gift
for the Empress Dowager.
It's trash now.
Master…
Master.
How many people know about this?
Only the escorts and me.
Don't
get the word out.
Get the best craftsmen
and remake it as soon as possible.
Master. These red leaves
are the finest rubies from Tazi.
Jubao House used all rubies on it.
We're out of stock.
What?
Then, go buy it.
If Prince Ying gets angry,
the Zheng family can't afford it.
These rubies are rare in Yangzhou.
Due to the rampant bandits in Hexi,
there are few merchants.
I'm afraid only Zhenlang Pavilion has them
in Yangzhou.
Zhenlang Pavilion.
Western Regions colored stones
are colorful.
But they are kitsch.
They are no match
for Central Plains jewelry.
Mr. Zheng, you're right.
Go there.
Whatever his conditions, promise him.
-Yes, Master. Yes, Master.
-Go.
What can I do for you?
What can you do for me?
I'm here to smash your shop. Get away.
I'll kill myself if you smash my shop.
Drop your hairpin.
I'm telling you. I don't care if you die.
Do you think I don't dare?
Shou.
Go out and close the door.
I'll play with her.
Okay.
I'll give you one last chance.
Drop your hairpin.
Let's talk about it. Here's the thing.
I was asked to do this.
I took the money to smash your shop.
If I don't smash it,
I'll lose my credit and my face.
And someone else
will mess with you. Right?
How about this? You pick
some of the cheapest jewelry.
Put away all the valuable jewelry.
Leave me with some cheap
and fragile jewelry.
So, I can take the money and look good.
You won't have big losses.
What do you say?
I'll close my eyes. I won't see it.
Okay?
Really?
Absolutely.
Don't move.
I didn't move.
Duanwu worked hard to get everything here.
I understand.
If you want to smash things,
smash this one.
-This?
-Will you smash it?
Miss, I…
I am the number one martial arts master
in the world.
I'm a man. Right?
I need respect.
You want me to smash this. How about this?
You pick something
that is a little more expensive than it.
I'll smash that. I'll make some noise.
So I can report it to my employer.
You won't have big losses.
Think about it.
Stay safe.
ZHENLANG PAVILION
Steward Zheng.
What's wrong…?
It's not a big deal.
Steward Zheng, what brings you here?
I want to talk to Mr. Yan
about a big deal.
Unfortunately,
Mr. Yan is not here.
If you want to talk about business,
you can talk to me.
Can you call the shots?
Of course.
Steward Zhao, let's talk in private.
Please.
I want 30 top-notch rubies.
Steward Zheng,
you came to the right person.
I can tell you that
only Zhenlang Pavilion has them
in Yangzhou.
But they are expensive.
One million cash.
Steward Zheng, you must be kidding.
Seventy million cash.
Good things are expensive.
Since you cannot decide,
you can consider it.
In that case, I'll leave.
Take care.
-Are you going to keep the store open?
-What's wrong?
-Huh?
-What happened?
Close your shop.
A woman wants to open a shop.
What's this?
CLEAR MIND
-They should learn some lessons.
-What is this?
A woman opening a shop is an insult
to the Yangzhou Jewelry Guild.
Steward Zheng.
ZHENLANG PAVILION
Mr. Qin.
How are you!
I heard that Zheng Wu
is a shareholder of Zhenlang Pavilion.
-A woman wants to open a shop.
-He put in a lot of effort
to support Lady Huan
at the Qionghua Festival.
Did they mess with rogues?
Ridiculous.
Parents are always in control
of the family property.
The Zheng family
will not invest in others.
He won't secretly support Clear Mind.
I'll tell my master about it.
We'll expose the Su's scams.
He's smashing hard.
Thank you, sir. Sir.
I have a question.
You're the owner of Baicaojing House.
Why are you picking on a little shop
that just opened?
Mind your business.
Don't poke around.
Animal.
There are some shops
on the east side of the city.
I'll go there tomorrow.
Remember. Buy something.
Okay, ma'ma.
Duanwu.
-What happened?
-Yunxiu.
It's okay.
Duanwu, it's fake. It's okay.
What about our jewelry?
Don't worry, Duanwu.
I put the jewelry away.
You went to buy gold and raw stones.
How's it going?
All the shops changed their minds.
Other shops refused to sell to us
as they knew we were from Clear Mind.
We must have been targeted.
What should we do?
Don't worry.
Let's clean it up first.
-Close the shop, Yingtao.
-Okay.
Ms. Su.
Have you encountered
any difficulties recently?
The decoration here
is special.
Garuda.
Learn from Ms. Su.
She doesn't follow the usual path.
Mr. Zheng, what brings you here?
I'm sorry you had to see this.
You opened your shop
opposite Zhenlang Pavilion.
You came up with the idea
of making jewelry out of shell shards.
Looks like you lost money.
But you became popular quickly.
You're smart.
I heard that the jewelry shops
are going to join forces
to cut off your supply chain.
As a shareholder, I'm worried.
Mr. Zheng, don't worry.
Clear Mind
-will think of a way.
-How?
You have no advantage in gold
or raw stones.
Now, you're suppressed.
Ms. Su.
How many months can you pay your rent?
I don't understand
what you mean.
Nothing.
I thought about what you promised me.
And now you're like this.
I'm here to advise you.
If you can't run the shop anymore,
close it before it's too late
and give me back my money.
I don't want to lose all my money.
The jewelry guild
is suppressing my Clear Mind.
As the largest shareholder,
you should be helping me
instead of mocking me.
Su Muzhe.
If you're not capable
and depend on me for everything,
why should you take 40% of the shares?
Why are you standing here today?
You're right.
I finally opened Clear Mind.
I don't want it to be like this.
I'll think of a way.
I don't have the patience for this.
Give back my money.
It's five million cash with interest.
I'll come to get the money later.
Master.
I didn't see Yan Zijing.
Steward Zhao
asked for 70 million cash for it.
I can't decide.
I asked around at other shops.
Some shops don't have it.
Some are not good enough
for the Empress Dowager.
Prince Ying has told the Empress Dowager
about the Red Leave Crown.
We have to make it at any cost.
We've spent a lot on the Red Leave Crown.
We have financial difficulties…
-Those goods…
-No.
Prince Ying has warned us.
He must have a reason.
We shouldn't act recklessly.
It's too late to change it
like we used to.
I'll talk to Yan Zijing.
See if we can pay later.
Master, I heard a rumor today.
It's said that Zheng Wu
is a shareholder of Zhenlang Pavilion.
He helped Lady Huan
win the top beauty title
at the Qionghua Festival.
I knew it.
Clear Mind wouldn't have so much money.
Zheng Wu is stupid.
All he knows is to enjoy life.
He doesn't understand business.
He must have been deceived by that girl.
Neither of my sons
would give me a break.
Mr. Zheng,
it's an honor to have you here.
Mr. Yan, I'm flattered.
What brings you here?
I urgently need some rubies.
I asked around
and came to you.
We are in the same ship.
If you help me today,
I'll repay you later.
Don't worry.
I'll see you right.
I'm sorry.
I don't get it.
You were not interested
in Western Regions colored stones
at the guild meeting the other day.
Why do you want so many rubies today?
Mr. Yan.
Do you want me to apologize to you?
-No.
-Do me a favor.
I'll pay you 50 million cash
in three months.
Mr. Zheng, don't make fun of me.
You know the industry rule.
Cash on delivery.
You're the guild lead.
You won't break the rules, right?
To be honest,
someone booked my rubies.
We have agreed on the price.
It's just that we didn't sign a contract.
Who booked them?
Forget it.
Since you're here, I'll please you.
I'll break my contract.
I'll sell these goods to you.
But the price remains the same.
Seventy million cash in three days.
Cash on delivery.
If you can't pay me in three days,
I'll sign a contract with them.
They pretended.
That man was foolish.
If he had been ordered to smash my shop,
he wouldn't have left so easily .
Yunxiu.
If I'm going out,
I'll leave Yingtao with you.
You should be careful.
If he comes again, I won't let him go.
Duanwu.
If you're not in the shop,
I'll guard it for you.
I'm relieved to have you there.
Well.
These are the materials
damaged in transit.
It's a waste to throw them away.
Can we use them?
Look at this broken gold jewelry.
We can smelt it,
make a design,
and make it into new jewelry.
We can take off the jewelry on it
and use it elsewhere.
This one is slightly damaged.
We can fix it.
Look.
Fill it…
There must be a lot of girls in Yangzhou
who have jewelry
that needs to be repaired.
We can
recycle their old jewelry
and transform it.
Yingtao, put out a new sign tomorrow
saying that we recycle jewelry
and reinvent the style.
By the way, buy some old jewelry.
We can use it as a raw material.
We can get through this.
Will it work?
Duanwu is always right.
Okay, I'll make the sign tomorrow.
Father.
Si.
It's late. We'll talk about it tomorrow.
I heard that our treasure was ruined.
I have an idea.
Si.
How did you know about that?
Father. I heard
you shut down a business
you had been running for a long time.
I'm worried
that we have financial problems.
In my opinion, we can ask others…
-Si, don't talk nonsense.
-Come on in.
Father.
Yuqing.
-Guard outside.
-Yes, sir.
Why are you here again?
Do you want to smash our shop again?
Yes.
I'll smash this shop
again.
Who is that?
I dare you
to smash my shop.
Put down the broom. Careful.
Your broom.
Duanwu.
He is the number one martial arts master
in the world.
He came to smash our shop again.
You smashed my shop, right?
Nice to meet you. Nice to meet you.
Smash it.
Well.
Don't smash gift boxes today. Thank you.
Smash it.
Shou.
Go out and close the door.
I'll smash the shop
again.
Okay.
I can't do this.
It's not good to hit people.
Are you going to make a living
from this for the rest of your life?
You don't have a wife or children, right?
My boss said
a man must have ambition.
Yingtao, I have a lot of work
to do back there.
I'll get to work.
I'll leave him to you.
Okay, Yunxiu.
-Miss.
-My name is Yingtao.
Ms. Yingtao.
To be honest,
my cousin committed a crime.
I need money urgently.
But I don't have money.
I had no choice but to agree with Mr. Qin
to do this kind of thing.
I…
How about this?
You hang out on the streets.
You must know a lot of news.
Help us to find out
who has jewelry that we don't want.
I'll ask my boss to give you commission.
Miss, what do you mean?
You…
Do you want me
to become a good person?
-I didn't mean it.
-Then…
-Let's go.
-Where are we going?
Smash the shop.
Smash the shop?
There is a lot of waste wood
in the backyard. You can smash it.
Ms. Yingtao, it's not good.
What do you tell your employer
if you don't smash it?
Yingtao.
Lady Xue, you're here.
What are you happy about?
Tell me about it.
Nothing.
Are you here to buy jewelry?
We have new ones.
I looked at the jewelry
I bought last time.
It doesn't compliment my complexion.
Do you want to return it?
You can return it.
Ms. Su told us
that the songstresses
should wear the latest jewelry.
If you don't like it anymore,
you can return it.
We only charge a 30% depreciation fee.
Thirty percent?
That's too much.
If I put the jewelry I wore
in your shop, there would be
a lot of people rushing to buy it.
You want to charge me a depreciation fee.
If you think the depreciation fee
is too much,
you can trade it for a new one.
It's worth 80% of its price.
In that way, you can buy new jewelry
for very little money.
Trade in old for new.
It's a good deal.
You mention Ms. Su in every sentence.
Have you become an employee of Clear Mind?
Lady Xue, I came to Clear Mind.
I have to make a living from it.
Do you want me to depend on you
for the rest of my life?
All right. You're thinking about me.
Take a 20% depreciation fee.
Ten percent.
Lady Xue, I can't.
I think about you.
But there are rules in the shop.
I can't decide.
How about this?
If you have any outdated jewelry,
you can trade it for a new one.
But you need to promote Clear Mind
among the songstresses.
With your reputation,
everyone will respond to your call.
If the price is good,
we'll give you a commission.
Yingtao.
You're so right not to be a songstress.
Forget it.
I'll think of it
as supporting my own business.
However.
How much is the commission?
It depends on the price.
Okay. It's a good thing
to wear new jewelry.
-I'll handle it.
-Thank you, Lady Xue.
Show me the jewelry.
Come here.
These are new pieces of jewelry.